

PEDRO PEIRANO PRAT

Front-end Developer Jr. React - MERN Stack

Personal Information

Full name: Pedro Peirano Prat

Birthdate: 22/11/1992

Place of residence: Rosario, Santa Fe, Argentina

Nationality: Argentine & Spanish

Contact Information

+549-341-5107560

pedro.peirano.prat@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/pedro-peirano-prat https://pedropeiranoprat.tech/

Educational History

HIGH SCHOOL & SPANISH BACHILLER

Parque de España Institute, Rosario

ARCHITECTURE DEGREE - 3° YEAR

Entry 2016 - 2019 Last year of study Facultad de Arquitectura, Planeamiento y Diseño - U.N.R.

Areas of expertise

HTML5 REACT
CSS3 NODE.JS
JAVASCRIPT ES6 MONGODB
JQUERY FIREBASE
NSQL GRAPHQL

FRAMEWORK7 SCRUM (AGILE METH.)

GIT CMD / GITHUB MDBOOTSTRAP/MATERIALIZE

IT Studies

COMUNIDAD IT - MOBILE

APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER

February 2020 - May 2020. Rosario, Santa Fe, Argentina Intensive on-site course - 9 hs per week for 3 months

- HTML5 CSS3 JAVASCRIPT JOUERY NSQL
- FIREBASE -FRAMEWORK7 -APACHE CORDOVA/PHONEGAP
- SCRUM (METODOLOGÍAS ÁGILES) KANBAN

FINAL PROJECT:

JOYRIDE - Maps navigation w/ GPS and proximity alarm

- HERE Maps API.
- Cordova Geolocation Plugin
- Framework7.
- https://github.com/peter-p-prat/Joyride

Ongoing studies

REACT - THE COMPLETE GUIDE: HOOKS CONTEXT REDUX MERN +15 APPS (UDEMY)

Started in July 2020. Online course

556 classes - 41 hs - Dictaded by Juan Pablo de la Torre Valdez

- HOOKS CUSTOM HOOKS STYLED COMPONENTS REDUX
- NodeJS MERN ContextAPI GATSBY GRAPHQL MongoDB
- REST API FETCH API AXIOS NextJS FIREBASE

ADVANCED CSS AND SASS FLEXBOX, GRID, ANIMATIONS AND MORE (UDEMY)

Started in December 2020. Online course

126 classes - 28 hs - Dictated by Jonas Schmedtmann

About me

I am a proactive person wishful to develop professionally. I have been in positions of responsibility for many years and have experience in working under pressure. I have a profile marked by resolution capacity and creativity.

In 2019, I discovered my passion for Software Development and it has become my life project, constantly improving my knowledge in FullStack development (JS ES6, Node.js, React.js, CSS3, JSX) with intensive on-site courses, online courses and developing personal projects. My greatest desire is to get my first IT job to meet new challenges and be part of a Development Team.

Work experience

REAL ESTATE MANAGEMENT AND ADMINISTRATION - REMOTE WORK

April 2016 - December 2020. Maldonado, Uruguay - Rosario, Santa Fe, Argentina

Remote work as collection manager for real estate entrepreneurship "Altos de Maldonado" by the company Lotibell S.A.

Contact: altosdemaldonado@gmail.com - +598 95 13 5555 Tasks:

- Manage current accounts.
- Calculate debts.
- Emit account statements
- Emit quarterly income reports and Cash Flow.

PERSONAL ENTREPRENEURSHIP OF DESIGN AND HOUSE RESTORATION

September 2018 - May 2020. Rosario, Santa Fe, Argentina

Revaluation of homes, interior design, construction of galleries and greenhouses.

Tasks:

- Deal with clients.
- Remodeling and improvements designs according to the needs and possibilities of clients.
- Execute restorations and constructions.
- Hiring freelance staff to delegate part of the work.
- Final quality control and presentation.

SAILING INSTRUCTOR - Y.C.R - C.V.R

April2014 - June 2018. Rosario, Santa Fe, Argentina

Founding instructor of the 29er Rosario School, together with the Santa Fe Sailing Association.

Tasks

- Teach technical knowledge in extreme weather conditions.
- Class planning.
- Being responsible for the safety of the fleet both in rivers and on the high seas.
- Group management in situations of risk, pressure and frustration.
- Study of student aptitudes to enhance them.
- Recognition and prevention of potential dangers.

Other skills

- Intermediate English First Certificate in English.
- Intermediate Portuguese (Parque de España Institute).
- Adobe Photoshop/ Adobe Illustrator.
- Group management in crisis situations.
- Ability to analyze complex technical information.
- Detailed and very self-demanding.
- Creative.
- Respectful and responsive to teamwork.
- Great sense of responsibility.